alright so welcome back once again if
you're someone new to my channel my name
is niklish and i live here in berlin if
you're someone who's looking for
admission in 2022
winter intake there's still some time
left for you if you're someone who's
still currently in your last semester
and because of corona things are getting
delayed and your results are going to
come late don't worry there is still
some time left for you to apply for
winter intake 2022. if you want any help
in terms of admission process and stuff
you can book the appointment directly
with me and i can help you to accelerate
the entire process for you so talking
about india yes i am coming very very
soon to india there is a google form in
this description of this video uh if you
want to register yourself for the event
i am conducting event in about
30 cities of india uh beside india i
will also be going to
dubai dhaka and kathmandu if you are
someone who is watching me from there
please go ahead and register yourself in
the google form this entire video is
exactly about this whole meetup what
i've kept so this entire event i've
named this as a german education summit
2022 conducted by nick sharla so to
register for this event there is total
of three steps in place one is first
you're going to fill out the google form
which is in the description of this
video second is you will receive a
payment link because the event is paid
third is your tickets will come with you
with three things location which is the
venue or the time and the date when the
event is going to happen the location
date and time is not yet decided the
only hint i can give you is probably the
event is going to start in the month of
june the rest of the information will be
shared to students who have registered
in the google form there are three
different types of events i am
conducting students who want to study
masters here in germany students who
want to study bachelors here in germany
and then the third category is people
who are looking for jobs directly what
they can do to actually enhance their
chances to get a full-time job directly
from india itself one very very big
disclaimer unless and until i have 50
registrations minimum in a particular
city i won't be able to conduct the
event basically june is probably the
date where i'm thinking to fly to india
and by that time if each of these cities
what i'm going to mention have at least
minimum 50 registration then only the
event will happen otherwise we'll have
to cancel that in case you have
made the payment already now then we
will just quickly refund you back your
money and then yeah either you come and
join us to the nearest city where the
event is actually happening or will have
to return your money back basically so
that's why it's very important that you
share this video's link uh to as many
people as you can if you're going to
german
classes shared there if you're in a
university share it there so yeah so as
i said the meetup is for two categories
of people one is job seekers and the
others are students so i've done
something like this in 2019 i don't know
if you uh are still watching me and if
you attended that event especially for
students the reason i've kept at least
like 500 rupees is because what i had
experienced in 2019 i mean imagine an
example of delhi there were almost like
1 500 people in front of a mall and i
could not even serve them and cater them
to their questions properly that's why
we want to do it in a proper setup so
the events which are happening for job
seekers are following cities mumbai
delhi bangalore chennai hyderabad
kolkata thiruvananthapuram pune and
kochi so these are the cities where i
will be having the job seekers event for
students the list is pretty long bear
with me
so it's dubai kathmandu dhaka and in
india it's
mumbai delhi bangalore chennai hyderabad
kolkata mdhabad
sorry i don't know if that's how it's
said but in goa indore surat raipur
nagpur and mysore
so these are the cities i will be coming
to your city but as i said i need at
least 50 registration minimum for us to
make the event happen so please go ahead
and share this event as much as you can
beside all of this since i'll be
traveling to so many different cities i
am totally open to come on to your
university campus you can go ahead and
talk to your professors
and host me onto your campus i'll be
happy to come there and talk about how
to study in germany for absolutely for
free and all the experiences i've gained
after traveling to almost 400 city
universities of germany so yeah there is
a lot of link in this description of
this video just to recap the
registration process so it starts with
google form then we will send you the
payment link and then third is you will
receive a ticket so yeah the ticket will
have all the details like location like
time uh the date the day all of that all
right so that's all from my side if you
like this video go ahead and hit that
thumbs up button i'll see you guys next
time bye